let questions = [
  {
  number: 1,
  question: "What is the tallest waterfall in Sri Lanka?",
  answer: "Bambarakanda Falls",
  options: [
    "Diyaluma Falls",
    "Bambarakanda Falls",
    "Rawana Falls",
    "Dunhida Falls"
  ]
},
{
  number: 2,
  question: "Who built the kingdom on Sigiriya rock?",
  answer: "King Kashyapa",
  options: [
    "King Kashyapa",
    "King Dathusena",
    "King Mahinda",
    "King Pandukabaya"
  ]
},
{
  number: 3,
  question: "When the worship period starts to worship Adams Peak?",
  answer: "December (Uduwap Poya day)",
  options: [
    "May (Vesak Poya day)",
    "December (Uduwap Poya day)",
    "April (Bak Poya day)",
    "September (Binara Poya day)"
  ]
},
{
  number: 4,
  question: "Who built the Octagonal Pavilion(Paththirippuwa) in The Temple of Tooth?",
  answer: "King Sri Wickrama Rajasingha",
  options: [
    "King Vijaya Rajasingha",
    "King Sri Wickrama Rajasingha",
    "King Keerthi Sri Rajasingha",
    "King Rajadhi Rajasingha"
  ]
},
{
  number: 5,
  question: "Who built the Galle Fort?",
  answer: "Portuguese",
  options: [
    "Portuguese",
    "Dutch",
    "British",
    "Chinese"
  ]
},
{
  number: 6,
  question: "Which district is the Nallur Kandaswamy Kovil located?",
  answer: "Jaffna",
  options: [
    "Colombo",
    "Kandy",
    "Jaffna",
    "Galle"
  ]
},
{
  number: 7,
  question: "Who was the king of Sri Lanka when bought Jaya Sri Maha Bodhi to Sri Lanka?",
  answer: "King Devanampiya Thissa",
  options: [
    "King Ashoka",
    "King Devanampiya Thissa",
    "King Dutugamunu",
    "King Gotabaya"
  ]
},
{
  number: 8,
  question: "Where is the Nine Arch Bridge located?",
  answer: "Ella",
  options: [
    "Badulla",
    "Ella",
    "Jaffna",
    "Haputhale"
  ]
},
{
  number: 9,
  question: "What is the tallest Mountain in Sri Lanka?",
  answer: "Piduruthalagala",
  options: [
    "Adams Peak",
    "Hanthana",
    "Piduruthalagala",
    "Pidurangala"
  ]
},
{
  number: 10,
  question: "What is the longest River in Sri Lanka?",
  answer: "Mahaweli River",
  options: [
    "Kelani River",
    "Mahaweli River",
    "Nilwala River",
    "Kalu River"
  ]
},  
];